http://www.dallaskenpo.com/privacy-policy/

HomeNews
Latest Dojo NewsPunch! Newsletter
Kids
New Student SignupClass Schedules3 Steps to a Great KidKids Kenpo Karate
Kids Promotional TestingReading & Report ListThe Annual Kenpo Invitational Kids Karate Tournament
New Student SignupClass SchedulesAdult Kenpo Karate
Family Tree & Black BeltsInstructor TrainingReading & Report List
Kung FuFitness ClassesSelf-Defense WorkshopsPrivate LessonsDownloadsAffliliate SchoolsAffiliate Martial Arts
Camps & Parties
Thanksgiving CampWinter CampRemote Homeschool CampOnline Karate CampsKids CampsKarate Birthday Parties!
Student PortalEvents
Dojo Event CalendarWomen’s Self Defense & Stranger Danger – Spring 2020Annual Mizutaki DinnerKeepers of the Flame 2020 – ONLINEOther Events
About
ContactAbout Chamberlain StudiosNew Student SignupTuitionClass SchedulesLocations
Love Field DojoLakewood DojoNorth Richland Hills DojoAfter School KarateAffiliated Schools
InstructorsPress & Media CoveragePhotosVideos
our Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us.
Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense is located at:
Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense
2739 Bachman Dr Dallas
75220 – Texas , United States
214-351-5367
It is Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to dallaskenpo.com (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “dallaskenpo.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on http://dallaskenpo.com blog posts. Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense’s websites choose to interact with Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense in ways that require Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at http://dallaskenpo.com to provide a username and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Advertisements
Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
Aggregated Statistics
Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense uses cookies to help Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense identify and track visitors, their usage of http://dallaskenpo.com, and their website access preferences. Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense’s use of cookies.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense’s sole discretion. Chamberlain Studios of Self-Defense encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
